(Sheldon-bot:)No, you can't.
(Leonard:)Wait.
(Sheldon-bot:)Come back.
(Sheldon-bot:)Halt.
(Sheldon-bot:)Authorized personnel only!
(Penny:)So, either one
of you weirdos
(Penny:)want to buy my underwear?
Only 1,400 bucks.
(Scene:)Sheldon,
this is ridiculous.
(Sheldon:)I'm behind you.
(Sheldon:)Please look at me when
you're talking to me.
(Leonard:)I am looking at you.
(Sheldon:)No, you're not.
(Sheldon:)Pay no attention to
that man in the bed.
(Leonard:)You cannot exist
(Leonard:)as a virtual presence.
(Leonard:)Not here
and certainly not at work.
(Leonard:)Oh, good God.
(Sheldon:)At my age,
do you know
(Sheldon:)how I'm statistically
most likely to die?
(Leonard:)At the hands of your roommate?
(Sheldon:)An accident.
(Leonard:)That's how I'm going
to make it look.
(Sheldon:)Until I can transfer
my intellect
(Sheldon:)to a more durable container,
(Sheldon:)my body will remain
safely ensconced in my bed.
(Leonard:)Fine, but don't expect my help.